Listen, so what, so what if you and I are different?
This doesn't scare me at all.
But I'm afraid of losing you.
Very.
You know me.
I will remain silent until the last moment,
because...
Well, I'm just not emotionally mature
and with the exact source of your discomfort,
who doesn't know how to talk about his feelings.
Maybe because I'm a hardcore loner
and that's no excuse.
I just...
I should have told you a long time ago
that you are the best thing that has ever happened to me in my life.
But no, I'm better...
I'll piss off your ears, I'll tell you that you're trying too hard,
although in reality I’m just very worried about you,
because no one in this world
doesn't mean more to me than you, Judy.